const sampleResults = [
    {
        "category"         : "Music: 80's Music",
        "type"             : "multiple",
        "difficulty"       : "hard",
        "question"         : "What date di MTV makes it's debut?",
        "correct_answer"   : "August 1, 1981",
        "incorrect_answers": ["January 1, 1981", "July 4, 1981", "October 31, 1981"]
    },
    {
        "category"         : "Entertainment: Music",
        "type"             : "multiple",
        "difficulty"       : "easy",
        "question"         : "Who was the lead singer of Motley Crue?",
        "correct_answer"   : "Vince Neil",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Sammy Hagar", "Jon Bon Jovie", "Dean Cain"]
    },
    {
        "category"         : "Entertainment: Music",
        "type"             : "multiple",
        "difficulty"       : "medium",
        "question"         : "What is the 80's famous MAX HEADROME (the computer reincarnation) name come from _______ ?",
        "correct_answer"   : "Edison Carter",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Piston", "Drive shaft", "Crankshaft"]
    },
    {
        "category"         : "Entertainment: Music",
        "type"             : "multiple",
        "difficulty"       : "easy",
        "question"         : "Who was the lead singer of Motley Crue?",
        "correct_answer"   : "Vince Neil",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Sammy Hagar", "Jon Bon Jovie", "Dean Cain"]
    },
    {
        "category"         : "Entertainment: Music",
        "type"             : "multiple",
        "difficulty"       : "easy",
        "question"         : "Who was the lead singer of Motley Crue?",
        "correct_answer"   : "Vince Neil",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Sammy Hagar", "Jon Bon Jovie", "Dean Cain"]
    },
    {
        "category"         : "Entertainment: Music",
        "type"             : "multiple",
        "difficulty"       : "easy",
        "question"         : "Who was the lead singer of Motley Crue?",
        "correct_answer"   : "Vince Neil",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Sammy Hagar", "Jon Bon Jovie", "Dean Cain"]
    },
    {
        "category"         : "Entertainment: Music",
        "type"             : "multiple",
        "difficulty"       : "easy",
        "question"         : "Who was the lead singer of Motley Crue?",
        "correct_answer"   : "Vince Neil",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Sammy Hagar", "Jon Bon Jovie", "Dean Cain"]
    },
    {
        "category"         : "Entertainment: Music",
        "type"             : "multiple",
        "difficulty"       : "easy",
        "question"         : "Who was the lead singer of Motley Crue?",
        "correct_answer"   : "Vince Neil",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Sammy Hagar", "Jon Bon Jovie", "Dean Cain"]
    },
    {
        "category"         : "Entertainment: Music",
        "type"             : "multiple",
        "difficulty"       : "easy",
        "question"         : "Who was the lead singer of Motley Crue?",
        "correct_answer"   : "Vince Neil",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Sammy Hagar", "Jon Bon Jovie", "Dean Cain"]
    },
    {
        "category"         : "Entertainment: Music",
        "type"             : "multiple",
        "difficulty"       : "easy",
        "question"         : "Who was the lead singer of Motley Crue?",
        "correct_answer"   : "Vince Neil",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Sammy Hagar", "Jon Bon Jovie", "Dean Cain"]
    }
];